{
  "subTitle": "",
  "items": [
    {
      "question": "1pm DOORS OPEN!",
      "answer": "1st 20 attendees get raffle ticket"
    },
    {
      "question": "1:30pm Kickoff/Keynote",
      "answer": "'A Well Balanced Nerd' By W. Garrett Myler @ Chapel (Broadcast)"
    },
    {
      "question": "2pm Talk: FDM vs Resin 3D Printing",
      "answer": "By Spencer Glancy @ Fortress of Solitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "2:15 Lightsaber Show/Demo",
      "answer": "@Exhibit Hall"
    },
    {
      "question": "2:25pm GIVEAWAY #1",
      "answer": "@Chapel (Broadcast)"
    },
    {
      "question": "2:30pm Talk: Starting a Comic Book Collection on a Budget",
      "answer": "By Paul Kailiponi @ Fortress of Solitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "3:00pm Panel Discussion: Nerd Culture",
      "answer": "Moderated by Kayla, Brooke, Quinn, & Jerry @ Fortress of Solitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "3:25pm GIVEAWAY #2",
      "answer": "@Chapel (Broadcast)"
    },
    {
      "question": "3:30pm Talk: Tabletop Wargames: From Beginner to Advanced",
      "answer": "By Raul Mundy @ Chapel"
    },
    {
      "question": "4:00pm Pokemon: From Games to Cards‚Äù",
      "answer": "@Fortress of Solitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "4:35pm GIVEAWAY #3 / Closing Remarks",
      "answer": "@Chapel (Broadcast)"
    }
  ]
}
